const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '217 + 188 =', answer: '405', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '216 + 189 =', answer: '405', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '328 + 177 =', answer: '505', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '146 + 159 =', answer: '305', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '356 + 149 =', answer: '505', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '416 + 289 =', answer: '705', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '438 + 167 =', answer: '605', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '519 + 186 =', answer: '705', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '519 + 286 =', answer: '805', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '538 + 367 =', answer: '905', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];